Hey, so I'm hella busy, but I just wanted to address this so that you all could tell your
friends. I am absolutely waiting for these protests to also happen in the Republican spaces.
So I wish these were bots, but they're not. They're actually real people. So one, Republicans
are not on a book tour right now. They're not on a book tour pretending like they weren't
a part and parcel to a genocide. So that's one. Two, Republicans don't come outside because
they're afraid. That's why you had all these Republican senators and representatives who
were being protested have cops at their forums to literally take people out. So the other part of
this is that this is Code Pink doing this protest and it's Code Pink who posted this. Do you think
Republicans are going to post people protesting them? You know, maybe you don't care if a genocide
continues, but many of us do. And so we're not going to be quiet until it stops. Many of us know
that it is continuing to make these people uncomfortable who still have power, no matter
how much they pretend they don't. It is continuing to make these headlines and to make people like you
know that it's still happening that keeps it in the present zeitgeist. And that presence is what is
going to make it actually have to get dealt with. So now, you know, and you don't have to ask
these questions anymore. Also, do y'all see how good my life's look? Flourishing.
Sister Seals. This is your ancestor, Harriet Tubman.